https://www.energycharter.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
Toggle navigation
ProcessOverviewFrequently Asked QuestionsEuropean Energy Charter (1991)Energy Charter Treaty (1994)Energy Charter TreatyEnergy Efficiency ProtocolTrade AmendmentInternational Energy Charter (2015)Overview1st Anniversary of The Hague II ConferenceReviewWhat we doInvestmentOverviewEnergy Investment Risk Assessment (EIRA)Industry Advisory PanelThe 'Blue Book'Investment Thematic ReportsInvestment Climate and Market StructureInvestment Promotion CentreTrade and TransitOverviewModel AgreementsTrade AmendmentRegional Energy Task ForceCross Border PipelinesTransit ProtocolTrade and Transit Thematic ReportsEnergy EfficiencyOverviewEnergy Efficiency Thematic ReportsEnergy Efficiency Country ReviewsDACO ProjectDispute SettlementOverviewAmicable Resolution of DisputesConflict Resolution CentreAll Investment Dispute Settlement CasesAccess to Travaux PréparatoiresCONEXOOverviewRegional activitiesEnergy Charter Liaison EmbassiesKnowledge CentreOverviewTraining ProgrammesBeijing Research CentreOccasional PapersInfographicsNewsletterEnergy Charter AwardConference DecisionsDocumentsWho we areInstitutionsEnergy Charter ConferenceMembers & ObserversSubsidiary BodiesOverviewStrategy GroupModernisation GroupWorking Group on Governance IssuesImplementation GroupBudget CommitteeLegal Advisory CommitteeIndustry Advisory PanelLegal Advisory Task ForceSecretariatOverviewSecretary GeneralStaffJobs/VacanciesCall For ProposalsMediaAll NewsAll EventsAll PublicationsExternal MediaContactPartnersOverviewEU4EnergyOverviewDACO ProjectDelegateGo
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyThe Energy Charter Secretariat (“ECS”) operates this website. This Privacy Policy page informs you of our policy regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal data we receive from users of this website.
The ECS respects and protects the privacy of its users and ensures that any personal data users may share remains private and is used only in strict accordance with this Privacy Policy.
In using this website, including any of the text, multimedia, data or other content made available on or through this website, users:agree to the collection and use of information of their personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy;
acknowledge that they have fully read and understood and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy; acknowledge and agree that Information available on this website is the valuable property of the ECS, and the ECS retains copyright, database rights and any other applicable intellectual property rights in this respectInformation Collection and Use
For the purposes of website traffic analysis, technical support and for securing and maintaining the ECS website, a log of all visits to the website is maintained. When users visit the website to read or download information, the ECS will collect and store only the following information through ©Google Analytics: date and time, originating IP address, domain name, type of browser and operating system used (if provided by the browser), URL of the referring page (if provided by the browser), object requested and completion status of the request.
The information is anonymously recorded and is used and analysed only at an aggregate level; none of it is reviewed at an individual level.
Subscription to the ECS newsletter and use of the contact form
Subscription to the ECS newsletter is optional. If you choose not to subscribe or provide personal information, you can still use the ECS website.
The ECS may use your personal data provided in the contact form or via the subscription to contact you with newsletters and information on publications, events and other information related to the work of the ECS.
These personal data and any information concerning users are used only for the specific advertised purpose, and will not be disclosed to third parties for commercial purposes.
All ECS officials and non officials who have access to the personal data stored on the website are obliged to respect the confidentiality of such data. The ECS will make a genuine effort to respond in a timely manner to any of your requests or to correct inaccuracies in your personal data.
At any time, you may request:the deletion or correction of your personal data. For such requests, please contact legalaffairs@encharter.org. the un-subscription of your e-mail address directly on the website or by sending an email to info@encharter.org.Communication with delegates
The ECS may use your personal data to contact you with information related the official meetings and documents of the Conference and its subsidiary bodies, as well as newsletters, publications and other events of the ECS.
Delegates are invited to access their Profile created in the protected area of the Site (“Delegates area”) to access information specifically aimed at direct communication between the ECS and delegates. The personal data of the delegates is strictly used for this specific purpose, and will not be disclosed to third parties for commercial purposes. A delegate can at any time update/modify/delete his or her profile from the website.
All ECS officials and non officials who have access to the personal data stored on the Delegates area are obliged to respect the confidentiality of such data.
Cookies
Some features of the ECS website use its own cookies and third-party cookies to prepare statistical information and improve the user browsing experience.
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to the user’s browser from a website and stored on the user’s computer's hard drive.
Users have the possibility to accept or decline cookies. However, if declining the use of cookies, users may not be able to use some portions of the ECS website.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
The ECS reserves the right to update or change its Privacy Policy at any time and users should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the ECS website after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Contact us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please refer to legalaffairs@encharter.org.
Updated on 29 May 2018
See AlsoFrequently Asked QuestionsSocial Media
About this websiteTerms of UsePrivacy PolicySitemapContact Us
Subscribe
×
Delegates' Area
Enter your credentials below to get access to the restricted content
Login
Username:
Password:
Stay logged in:
Forgot your password?
Close
Proudly powered by Wikafi
